Guide to the Irish Immigration Reform Movement, New York Chapter Records AIA.016
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- III: Legislation, 1986-1990; 217474
  - H.R. 4300: Comparison to S. 358, 1990; 217680 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - H.R. 4300: Correspondence, 1990; 217682 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - H.R. 4300: Diversity Amendment, 1990; 217686 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - H.R. 4300: Immigration Task Force Hearing and Testimonies I, Mar 1, 1990; 217683 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - H.R. 4300: Immigration Task Force Hearing and Testimonies II, Mar 1, 1990; 217684 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - H.R. 4300: Lobbying Plan, 1990; 217685 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - H.R. 4341: Kennedy, Sen. Edward, (MA) "Legalization Extension Act of 1988", 223027 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - H.R. 5115: Donnelly, Rep. Brain (MA), Comments "Legal Immigration Amendments of 1988", 223028 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - H.R. 5115: "Immigration and Nationality Act", Revision, 1987; 223037 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - H.R. 5115: "Immigration and Nationality Act", Markup, Notes, Sep 30, 1988; 223036 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - H.R. 5115/S. 2104: Comparison, 1988; 223038 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - H.R. 5115/S. 2104: IIRM Testimony, Sep 16, 1988; 223039 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - H.R. 5115: Testimony, Don Martin (IIRM), Sep 1989; 223040 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - H.R. 5115: Testimony Hearing Notes, Don Martin (IIRM), Sep 1989; 223041 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - H.R. 5229/H.R. 672: Berman Bill (Rep. Howard Berman, CA)-"Legal Immigration Reform Act of 1989", 223042 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - P.L.100-658 Berman/Donnelly:, 1989; 223043 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - S. 358:Kennedy/Simpson Bill, "Immigration Act of 1989" (Senator Alan Simpson, R-WY), 223044 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - S. 358: Kennedy/Simpson/Berman/Gilman, 1988-1989; 233213 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - S. 358/H.R. 672/H.R. 2448/H.R. 2646: Hearing; Testimony I, Sep 27, 1989; 233214 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - S. 358/H.R. 672/H.R. 2448/H.R. 2646: Hearing; Testimony II, Sep 27, 1989; 233215 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - S. 358: Testimony by IRRM, Sean Minihane (Simpson Bill), Mar 2, 1989; 233216 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - S. 358: Hearing, Mar 3, 1989; 233217 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - S. 358/H.R. 4165 (Morrison)/H.R. 672/H.R. 2448: Hearings, Mar 13, 1990-Mar 14, 1990; 233218 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - S. 448: Simon Bill (Sen. Paul Simon, IL) "Legal Immigration Reform Act of 1989", 233219 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - S. 1611/H.R. 3143: Kennedy/Donnelly Bill "Immigration Act of 1987", 233220 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - S. 1611/H.R. 3143: Kennedy/Donnelly Bill-Survey, 1987; 233221 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - S. 1611: Hearing;Testimony, Oct 23, 1987; 233222 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - S. 1611: Hearing; Testimony, Dec 11, 1987; 233223 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - S. 1611: "Immigration Act of 1988"; Kennedy/Simpson, 1987-1989; 233224 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - S. 1206: Helms Bill-"Immigration Reform Act of 1989" (Sen. Jesse Helms, R-NC), 233227 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - S. 2104/S. 358: Kennedy/Simpson Bill "Immigration Act of 1989" I, 233228 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - S. 2104/S. 358: Kennedy/Simpson Bill "Immigration Act of 1989" II, 233229 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - S. 2104/S. 358: Kennedy/Simpson Bill "Immigration Act of 1989" III, 233230 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - S. 2104/H.R. 5115: Hearing; Testimony, Sept 7, 1988; 233231 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - S. 2132/H.R. 4801: D'Amato/DioGuardi Bill (Rep. Alfonse D'Amato, NY; Rep. Joseph DioGuardi CT), 1986-1988; 233232 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- IV: Lobbying, 1984-1997; 217475
  - Advertising: Irish Voice, 1990; 233424 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Aer Lingus, 1988; 233425 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Alerts; Daily Faxes, 1990; 233426 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Alerts, Daily Faxes, General, 1997; 233427 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - American Immigration Institute, 1990; 233428 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - American Irish Legislators Association, 1988; 233429 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Amnesty, 1987-1988; 233430 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Area Intelligence (missing persons), 1988; 233431 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Brennan, Philomena (Irish Voice), 1986-1987; 233432 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Brooklyn Breakfast, Mar 4, 1990; 233433 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Catholic Charities, 1987; 233434 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Catholic Church: Migration and Refugee Services, National Office, 1988-1989; 233435 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Center for Immigration Rights, 1989-1992; 233436 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Center for Irish Immigration Studies, 1989; 233437 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Coalition of Irish Immigrant Centers-USA, 1997; 233438 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, 1988; 233439 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence I, 1989-1990; 233440 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence II, 1989-1990; 233441 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Irish Government, 1989; 233442 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: New York State Government, 1989; 233443 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Outgoing, 1988; 233444 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Response to Letter Writing Campaign, 1988; 233445 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Thank-yous, 1990; 233446 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Dail Debates: Transcripts I, 1987-1988; 233447 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Dail Debates: Transcripts II, 1987-1988; 233448 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Delegation to Ireland, 1989; 234439 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Discrimination Cases, 1988-1989; 233449 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Endorsement Letters, 1987; 233450 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - European Contacts, 1987; 233452 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Executive Office (President of the United States), 1988-1989; 233451 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Fianna Fail (Republican Party of Ireland), 1987-1988; 233453 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Fine Gael Emigration Committee, 1987-1989; 233454 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Fine Gael: Dukes, Alan, TD, 1988-1989; 236792 (Box 9, Folder 17a)
  - Flatley, Thomas: Correspondence, 1989-1990; 233455 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Flynn, Padraig: Minister for the Environment, 1988; 233456 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Friends of Ireland Ad Hoc Committee, 1988; 233457 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Gaelic Athletic Assocation, 1989; 233458 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Green Card Column, 1988; 233459 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Guinness: Correspondence, 1990; 233460 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - H.R. 4300, 1989-1990; 233461 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Harris Miller: Testimony, Drafts, Don Martin, 1988; 233462 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Haughey, Charles J. (Taoiseach): Correspondence; Speeches, 1987-1988; 233463 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Holt Miller: Morrison Hearings, 1988; 233464 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Holt Miller I, 1988; 233465 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Holt Miller II, 1988; 233466 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Holt Miller, 1989; 233468 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Holt Miller, 1989; 235576 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Holt Miller I, 1989; 233469 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Holt Miler II, 1989; 233471 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Holt Miller: Subcommittee on Europe and the Middle East Testimony, 1989; 233467 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Immigration Law Reform: General, 1988; 233581 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Immigration Reform and Control Act: Hispanic Organizations, 1988, undated; 233584 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Immigration Service Associates: Request for Lobbying Services, 1995-1996; 233582 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Irish Immigration Working Committee (IIWC), 1987-1988; 233583 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Irish American Unity Conference, 1987; 233585 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Irish Government, 1988-1989; 233587 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Irish Government Action Group: Correspondence; Meetings, 1987-1988; 233586 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Irish Publications List, circa 1988; 233588 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Koch, Edward (Mayor of New York City), 1988-1989; 233589 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Legal Associations, 1987-1997; 233590 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - "Legalize the Irish" Lyrics, Kevin Molloy, 1989; 233591 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Lenihan, Brian (Minister of Foreign Affairs, Ireland): Correspondence, 1987-1988; 233592 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Letter-Writing Campaigns, 1988-1989; 233593 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Letters to the Editor, 1987; 233594 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Media, 1987-1997; 233597 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Media Packet "Equality and Justice for All", 1988; 233598 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Membership: No Zip, circa 1987-1988; 233599 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Membership #1-100, circa 1987-1988; 233623 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Membership #101-200, circa 1987-1988; 233624 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Membership #201-300, circa 1987-1988; 233625 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Membership #301-400, circa 1987-1988; 233627 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Membership #401-500, circa 1987-1988; 233628 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Membership #501-600, circa 1987-1988; 233629 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Membership #601-700, circa 1987-1988; 233631 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Membership #701-800, circa 1987-1988; 233632 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Membership #801-900, circa 1987-1988; 233633 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Membership #901-1000, circa 1987-1988; 233634 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Membership #1001-1100, circa 1987-1988; 233635 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Membership #1101-1200, circa 1987-1988; 233636 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Membership #1201-1300, circa 1987-1988; 233637 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Membership #1301-1400, circa 1987-1988; 233638 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Membership Forms and cards (see also Box 14, folders 17, 18), circa 1987-1988; 233639 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Memberships I, 1987; 236092 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Memberships II, 1987; 236093 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Mercier Press, Dublin: Publication Materials, undated; 233641 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - National Lobbying Plan, 1988; 233667 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - National Lobbying Plan Mailout: Responses New York State, 1988; 233595 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - National Lobbying Plan Mailout: Responses-Other States, 1988; 233596 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - National Mailing, 1990; 233642 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - National Organization: Council Meetings, 1987-1988; 233643 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - National Organization: Council Meetings, 1989; 233644 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - National Organization: Branches, 1989-1990; 233647 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - National Organization: Branches, Memos to, 1989-1990; 233645 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - National Organization: Branches: Media and Communication, 1989; 233648 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - National Organization: California, 1988-1989; 233649 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - National Organization: Chicago Chapter, 1989-1990; 233650 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - National Organization: Connecticut I, 1989; 233651 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - National Organization: Connecticut II, 1988-1989; 233652 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - National Organization: Connecticut III, 1988-1989; 233653 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - National Organization: D.C., 1988-1989; 233654 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - National Organization: Delaware Valley Chapter, 1989-1990; 233655 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - National Organization: Dublin Office, 1988-1989; 233656 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - National Organization: Hudson Valley Chapter, 1989-1990; 233657 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - National Organization: Kansas, 1988; 233658 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - National Organization: Maryland, 1988-1989; 233659 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - National Organization: Massachusetts, 1987-1990; 233661 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - National Organization (National Network), 1990; 233646 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - National Organization: National Network Correspondence, 1990; 233668 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - National Organization: New Jersey, 1988; 233662 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - National Organization: Ohio (Cleveland), 1988; 233663 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - National Organization: Pennsylvania, Pittsburgh, 1990; 236751 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - National Organization: Rhode Island Chapter, 1989; 235598 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - National Organization: Suffolk County, 1988; 235599 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - National Organization: Texas, 1989; 233664 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - New Irish Action Group, 1987-1989; 233669 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - New York City Council Hearing: IIRM Testimony, Feb 8, 1989; 233670 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - New York City Government: Office of Immigration Affairs, 1988; 233671 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - New York City and New York State Government, 1988-1990; 233672 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - News/Alerts, 1984, 1987-1988; 233708 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Newsletter, 1989; 233711 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Newsletter, 1990; 233712 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Newsletter: Correspondence, Drafts of Articles I, 1989; 233709 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Newsletter: Correspondence, Drafts of Articles II, 1989; 233710 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Newsletter: Drafts, Enclosures, 1990; 233729 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - O'Neill, Fr. John: Direct Lobbying Efforts, undated; 233730 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Other Organizations: Immigration, 1988-1990; 233731 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Petitions (see also Box 15 for bulk of Petitions), 1988; 233761 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Petitions (see also Box 12), 1988; 234262 (Box 15, Folder 3-18)
  - Plan C: Australian Emigration, 1984-1986; 233762 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Political Action Committees: General, 1985-1989; 233732 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Press, 1988-1990; 233763 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Press Kit Materials, undated; 233764 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Press Releases, 1989, undated; 233765 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Press Releases, 1992; 235600 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Press Releases, Announcements, 1987-1988; 233766 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Press Releases: Emerald Isle Immigration Center (EIIC), 1991, undated; 233767 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Press Releases: Issued to Irish Papers, 1988-1989; 233768 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Press Releases, News, 1988-1989; 233769 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Progressive Democrats, 1988; 233770 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Public Relations: Grassroots, Startup, circa 1987; 233640 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Refugees: General, 1989; 233771 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Report: "Case for Immigration Reform" by IRRM; presented to Honorable Joseph A. Moakley Chairman, Committee on Rules, U.S. House of Representatives, Aug 1990; 233772 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Reports: New Irish in America, undated; 233773 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Research: Articles, 1987-1989; 233775 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Research: Reports, Statistics, 1987-1990; 233774 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Schumer Bill (Rep. Charles Schumer D-NY), 1988-1990; 233776 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Selective Service: National Guard; Military, 1986-1989; 233777 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Speeches: Unidentified, undated; 233780 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Statistics: Visas, Immigrants by Country, 1987-1989; 233778 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - "Undocumented Irish" Interim Paper by March B. Corcoran, Columbia University, Apr 1988; 233781 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Union of Students in Ireland, 1988; 233782 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - U.S. Immigration: General, 1988-1989; 233783 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Video Project, 1987; 233733 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Visas: Berman Visa Lottery, OP-1 Program, 1989; 233784 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Visas: Donnelly Visa Program NP-5, 1987-1990; 233785 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Visas: Donnelly Visa [Program] NP-5, Procedures, 1987; 233786 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Visas: Morrison Visa: Regulations, 1990-1991; 233787 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Visas: Morrison Visa AA-1 Visa, 1991; 233788 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Visas: Morrison Visa AA-1 Visa, 1991-1993; 233789 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Visas: Morrison Visa Winners [Lottery], 1984; 233790 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Visas: Transition-Walsh, 1998; 233791 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Visas: Visa Bulletin, 1988-1990; 233792 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Washington, DC Congressional Office Visits: Lobby Reports, Sep 1988; 236750 (Box 13, Folder 4A)
  - Washington, DC Congressional Office Visits, Jun 21, 1989; 233793 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Washingtion, DC Lobbying Day, Sep 18, 1990; 233796 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Washington, DC Trip, Mar 1990; 233795 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Washington, DC Trips, 1989-1990, undated; 233794 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - White House Conference, Sep 11, 1998; 233797 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - White Lung Association, 1989; 233798 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Workers Party, 1988; 233799 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- V: Publications, 1978-2000; 217476
  - Australia: A Handbook for Living and Working Down Under (Mercier Press), 1988; 234249 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Federal Statistics I, 1978, 1986-1987; 234251 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Federal Statistics II, 1978, 1986-1987; 234252 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Guidelines for Irish Immigrants, 1989; 234250 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Immigration and Nationality Act with Amendments and Notes on Related Laws--Committee Print Committee on the Judiciary (House) 7th ed. rev. Sep 1, 1980, 234253 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Immigration Policy, Congressional Research Service (CRS) Reports, 1986-1988; 234254 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Immigration Profiles: A Directory of Who's Who in Immigration (Washington Service Bureau Inc.), 1989; 234255 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Irish America Magazine, 1987-1988; 234299 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - "Irish and American Independence", undated; 234256 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Irish American Organizations, Various, 1987-1990; 234257 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Labor and Immigration Studies: Journals and Reports, 1988-1993; 234258 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - News Magazines, Various, 1988-1990; 234259 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - "Report of the Visa Office," U.S. Department of State, 1996; 234260 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - "Workforce 2000: Work and Workers for the 21st Century," U.S. Department of Labor, 1987; 234261 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Articles, 1985-1986; 236083 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Articles, 1987; 236084 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Articles, 1988; 236085 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Articles, Jan 1989-Apr 1989; 236086 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Articles, May 1989-Dec 1989; 236087 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Articles, 1990; 236088 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Articles, 1991-1993; 236089 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Articles, 1994-2007; 236090 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Articles, 2000; 236091 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Articles, undated; 236082 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Newspapers: Irish Echo, Mar 1988; 235985 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Newspapers: Irish Voice, Oct 1990-Dec 1990; 235986 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- VI: Nonprint materials, 1987-2007; 217477
  - Artwork :"Advisory Pamphlet for Irish Immigrants" Mylar Seal, 1987; 235983 (Box 19)
  - Computer Disk Indexes (includes documents), 1988; 234315 (Box 17)
  - "Legalize the Irish" Stickers, 1987-1989; 235984 (Box 19)
  - Office Materials, 1987-2007; 234307; Contains computer diskettes including 3 1/4 inch and 5" floppies; phone message book, call log book, hotline book circial 1988; official IRRM seal (broken); address stamp; "check endorsement" stamp; deposit only to Bank of Ireland stamp. (Box 18)
  - NY #1 Opening of EIIC Center, undated; 236955; 1 videocassette 1 VHS tape (Box 18)
  - "The New Irish in America: Living in the Shadows", undated; 584834; 1 videocassette 1 VHS tape (Box 18)
  - IIRM TV Programs Aerlingus Edits; New Irish Clips, Feb 17, 1939; 584835; 1 videocassette 1 VHS tape (Box 18)
  - IIRM New York Tape 4; RTE show Nick Murphy AOH, Jan 1987; 584836; 1 videocassette (Box 18)
  - IIRM Chicago Tape 1 Angela Buckley; from Boston Immigration Reform Movement television show, undated; 584837; 1 videocassette 1 VHS tape (Box 18)
  - CBS News Nightwatch, Oct 11, 1991; 584838; 1 videocassette 1 VHS tape (Box 18)
  - 3 dictaphone tapes, April 23; 584839 (Box 18)
  - "Tommy Mackem PSA for IIRM; Various Artists: Bringing it all Back (from the BBC TV series), undated; 584840; 2 audiocassettes 2 cassette tapes (Box 18)
  - Tommy Makem PSA with transcript, Sep 30, 1987; 584841; 1 reel to reel tape (Box 18)
  - "IIRM 20th Anniversary Parts I and II", Oct 25, 2007; 584842; 2 audiocassettes 2 mini-cassettes (Box 18)
  - Plaque: "The Irish Organization of the Year award" presented by the Irish American Heritage Committee, March 9, 1990, 236817 (Box 18)
  - Photographs: Hurley, Patrick, 1980s; 246315 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Photographs: Morrison, Bruce, 1980s; 246316 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Photographs: Various, including Brian O'Dwyer, Charles Schumer, Joseph Kennedy, 1989-1990; 246317 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Photographs: Various, including IIRM and EIIC staff, members of Congress, 1989-1991; 246318 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - T-shirt (1), Sweatshirts (2): "Irish Immigration Reform Movement" screenprint, 1987-1989; 235987 (Box 19)